nayavideo.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - NayaVideo

Privacy Policy

By using and visiting our website, you agree to the terms and conditions and Privacy policy of Nayavideo.com.Â 

These terms and conditions apply to all users, and if you don't agree to these terms then please don't use the website.Â 

Nayavideo.com has created this Privacy policy in order to demonstrate our determination to your online privacy.

What information do we collect:

We collect information when you register to our website. You may be asked to enter your name, your email address, your country name,Â 

your address and your telephone number (if required )

What do we use your information for?

We use your information just to enhance your experience and to improve our website.

Do we use Cookies?

Yes we use cookies in order to:

Count return visits to our site. Reporting anonymous statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage. Enabling automatic logins. Personalize the website and to deliver content specific to your interests. Enable Google analyzer to monitor traffic to our website.

Do we use Third Party Links:

No, we don't use third part links, unless they're our partners and we're bound to co-operate with each other. Parties other than our Partners are not allowed to share their links or promote there website without notifying us.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Information to outside parties/companies:

We donâ€™t disclose any personal information to third parties. Your information will not be shared to any third party.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:

If we want to change our privacy policy, weâ€™ll post it here.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
